[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Imperial machines are launched into space at the beginning of Episode V?", "correct_answer": "Probe Droid", "incorrect_answers": ["X-Wing Fighter", "Tie Intercepter", "Tie Fighter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the abbreviation AIDS actually stand for?", "correct_answer": "Acquired immune deficiency syndrome", "incorrect_answers": ["Acute immune deficiency symptom", "Acute immune deficient syndrome", "Acquired immune deficient symptom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the first Waynes World movie come out?", "correct_answer": "1992", "incorrect_answers": ["1988", "1994", "1990"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Songwriters Hall of  Fame located?", "correct_answer": "New York City, NY", "incorrect_answers": ["Detroit , Michigan", "Las Vegas, Nevada", "Chicago, Illinois"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the music for Brian de Palmas 2000 movie Mission to Mars?", "correct_answer": "Ennio Morricone", "incorrect_answers": ["Howard Shore", "Goran Bregovic", "Slash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official residence of the French Prime Minister?", "correct_answer": "Hotel Matignon", "incorrect_answers": ["Hotel Jacques Santer", "Hotel Poos", "Hotel Christia Grobet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rich soil may contain up to 100,000 earthworms per square acre.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Im gonna make him an offer he cant refuse is a quote from the 1972 movie The Godfather. What actor delivered the line?", "correct_answer": "Marlon Brando", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "Robert Duvall", "Al Pacino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Broccoli is very rich in vitamins and other essential nutrients. Which of these vitamins does broccoli contain?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin C", "Vitamin A", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pink ball is worth 6 points in the game of snooker.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the electromagnetic spectrum, which region is the most energetic?", "correct_answer": "gamma", "incorrect_answers": ["infrared", "ultra-violet (UV)", "radio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about Charles Darwins wife, Emma Wedgwood?", "correct_answer": "She was known for her charity work", "incorrect_answers": ["She was Charles second cousin", "She was two years older than Charles", "She was quick-tempered and often argued with her husband"]}]